Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXVI is arranged in 2 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXVII is arranged in 12 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXVIII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXV. AMERICAN RAILWAY EXPRESS COMPANY
  - Sub-Series 409-0. American Railway Express Company
    - General, 1928-1929 (Box 584, Folder 1)
- Series LXXVI. EMERGENCY BOARD
  - Sub-Series 413-0. Emergency Board
    - Report. Louisiana and Arkansas Railway Company. Louisiana, Arkansas, and Texas Railway Company, 1932 (Box 584, Folder 2)
      1932 March 10
  - Sub-Series 413-9. Emergency Board
    - Report. Southern Pacific Company. Northwestern Pacific Railroad Company, 1937 (Box 584, Folder 3)
      1937 April 14
- Series LXXVII. RAILWAY EXPRESS AGENCY, INC.
  - Sub-Series 414-0. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - General, 1929 (Box 584, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 414-1. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Employees, 1929 (Box 584, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 414-2. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Funds, 1929-1930 (Box 584, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 414-3. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Seniority Rosters, 1928-1929 (Box 584, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 414-5. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Use of Master Waybill -1934 (Box 584, Folder 8)
    - Use of Master Waybill -1931 (Box 584, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 414-6. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Collection of Carrying Charges, 1931 (Box 584, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 414-7. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Mutual Relief Association, 1932-1933 (Box 584, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 414-8. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Salaries of Officers, 1934 (Box 584, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 414-9. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Pickup Service by Western Union Employees, 1934-1935 (Box 584, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 414-10. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Express Shipments Transported by Railroad Freight, 1934 (Box 584, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 414-11. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Standard Agreement Between Railroads and Railway Express Agency, Inc., 1936 (Box 584, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 414-12. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Claim Bureau, 1947-1950 (Box 584, Folder 16)
- Series LXXVIII. MEMBERSHIP
  - Sub-Series 416-1. Membership
    - Twenty-Five Year Buttons, 1936-1959 (Box 584, Folder 17)